<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MRF UP &amp; UKZN 2018</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MRF UP &amp; UKZN 2018</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 22:26:09 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Keenan</title>
      <link>/blogs/keenan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/keenan/</guid>
      <description>Keenan&amp;rsquo;s question 1 Keenan&amp;rsquo;s responses will go here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thabo</title>
      <link>/blogs/thabo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/thabo/</guid>
      <description>1. What are you still learning and grappling with about yourself and how you tend to approach issues of reconciliation? I always begin any conversation around reconciliation by providing creating a foundation for discussion. In this context, I hold reconciliation- or the idea of it- as an end, not a means to an end. As a result, when it comes to matters of reconciliation, the first lens I use is racial given our historic past as a country and the loss of dignity as a people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linet</title>
      <link>/blogs/linet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/linet/</guid>
      <description>1. What are you still learning and grappling with about yourself and how you tend to approach issues of reconciliation? The ability to view reconciliation as a singular, subjective journey for all. There is a temptation to except everyone to view reconciliation in the same way e.g. repatriations for past wrongs, or recognition of privilege or even just having the same conversations surrounding the need for reconciliation. Sometimes, we expect too much from people – to see what we see or think how we think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>We are a group of scholars from two universities in South Africa, The University of Pretoria and the University of KwaZulu-Natal who have been selected as Mandela Rhodes Scholars for 2018. This has been way more than a scholarship opportunity. We have developed strong friendships, been exposed to new people, ideas, and thought processes, and challenged to our core on issues surrounding leadership, reconcilliation, entrepreneurship and education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuart</title>
      <link>/blogs/stuart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/stuart/</guid>
      <description>1. What are you still learning and grappling with about yourself and how you tend to approach issues of reconciliation? A major thing that I am still getting to grips with is understanding both sides of the enormity of the issue. I think a place to start here would be to wrestle with what does it mean to do wrong to someone? What is the aetiology of the underlying mechanism needing reconciliation?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>